qubee.com.pk 2018-12-22

# Privacy Policy | Qubee – Broadband Internet

**Qubee Privacy Policy**

Revised on 1st January, 2018

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) describes how information about you is collected, used, and disclosed by Qubee and provides other important privacy information, describes when and how we may change this Policy, and tells you how to contact us with any questions or comments.

**WHAT TYPES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU**

We collect information about you and your associated device(s) when you use our products or services or otherwise interact with us or with third-party services through our products and services. Examples of the types of information we collect include:

**Personal Information**

“Personal Information” means information that we directly associate with a specific person or entity (for example, name; addresses; telephone numbers; email address; location). Personal information does not include “de-identified,” “anonymous,” or “aggregate” information – which are not associated with a specific person or entity.

**Network and Device Information**

We may collect information about your use of our network associated with your account, device, and network performance information.

**Location Data**

We may collect your device’s location whenever it is turned on (subject to coverage limitations)

**HOW INFORMATION ABOUT YOU IS COLLECTED**

Qubee collects information about you in three primary ways:

**Information You Provide**

We collect information that you provide to us when you apply for, purchase, or use our services, or otherwise communicate with us.

For example, some of the ways you may provide information to us include:

  * When you sign up for our Internet services or purchase other products or services, we may collect personal contact details, email address and residential address.
  * When you establish or modify an online account, we may collect user identification information, passwords, and/or security question responses that you will use for future verification.
  * When you interact with our customer service representatives, we also collect Personal Information and other information to verify the user. We may monitor and record phone calls, e-mails, live chats, or other communications between you, your device, and our customer service representatives or other employees or representatives.

**IMPORTANT:** We do not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your Personal Information to unaffiliated third-parties (parties outside the Qubee family) to market their services or products to you without your consent.
